RANDY PANOPIO

randypanopio.github.io randypanopio@gmail.com 778 - 926 - 8693 Vancouver, B.C

I am a design oriented developer with a focus on building usable and maintainable tools. With a diverse background of user experience and web development, to cinematography and physical art. I try to bridge ideas and build sustainable products in all of the projects that I partake in.

Skills

Development

Languages: C#, .NET, Python, Java Tools: Powershell, Docker Web: JS, PHP, Angular Version Control: Git, Perforce, GitHub REST API Integration

Toolkit

Maya Scripting (MayaPy, PyMEL) DCC Tooling & Automations UI Dev (Web, PySide, Qt) Engines: Unity, Frostbite Procedural Content Generation Shaders (Shader Graphs)

Content Creation

Adobe Suite (Photoshop)
Texturing & Processing
3D Modeling (Maya, Blender)
Character Rigging
FK/IK Animations
Jira, Shotgrid (Integrations)

Methodologies

Test Driven Development Agile Methodology Iterative Design Process Pipeline Architecture Design UX/UI Design

Education

Simon Fraser University

Interactive Arts and Technology (SIAT), Bachelor of Science -Concentration of Interactive Systems

2015 - 2020

Work Experience

Electronic Arts Associate Technical Artist

Burnaby, British Columbia Sept 2021 - Feb 2023

Worked on pipeline tool development and management to deliver art assets from content creation to in game render. Supported multiple FIFA/FC titles including titles from 22, 23, the FC rebrand, FIFA Online, FIFA Mobile, and unreleased incubation football titles.

- Subject matter expert on content management and worked on designing and replacing the delivery pipeline, tripling the previous workflow's throughput and reducing process runtime from a 10 minute run down to 1 minute, while introducing previously unsupported content into this automated framework. Supporting over a hundred thousand unique files and assets per year.
- Improved and automated legacy pipelines, saving the team workflow capacity by up to 75% by eliminating manual workflows with automated pipelines, saving team members several hours during a typical work week.
- Collaborated and supported cross domain teams and multiple international teams to organize, process, and deliver content into the game while maintaining production timelines.
- Updated existing DCC tools and authored new tools to improve and automate repetitive tasks from artists and management, while training and supporting them with our production workflows and tools.

Under the GUI Academy Inc. **Programming Instructor**

Richmond, British Columbia

Dec 2020 - June 2021

Taught children ages 7 - 16 concepts of programming through hands on Unity and website projects during weekly online class sessions.

- Introduced concepts regarding programming foundations, web development, and game design to children with various skill levels
- Volunteered creating personalized coding challenges for advanced students who showed interest in expanding their programming repertoire

Safe Software Inc. Front-End Web Developer - Co-op

Surrey, British Columbia **May 2018 - Dec 2018**

Acted as a front-end developer and the primary interface designer, maintaining and building web interfaces for a suite of enterprise GIS management tools.

- Collaborated with a team of developers, product managers, and stakeholders working on a new core feature, on an enterprise web application used by over 10,000 organizations across the world
- Implemented three new UI for new features built upon existing management tools with over 100 individual UI elements within 3 design iterations, and completed the testing phase within 4 months.
- Worked in an agile and test-driven development environment, building upon a hybrid web framework application while authoring and maintained unit tests during production